projectplace.com 2006-06-19

# Projectplace - Privacy Statement

  * ### [Terms & Conditions](http://www.projectplace.com/terms.html)

|  | 

Projectplace International AB (hereinafter referred to as "Projectplace") has created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**Personal information and Information sharing**  
For each visit to our login page we automatically recognize your IP address, domain and Web browser. This information is not used to personally identify you. We use your IP address to help diagnose possible problems with our server farm and Internet connection. We do not sell or market this information to any third party. We do however, on occasion, aggregate this information internally and analyse it to help improve the performance of our service. 

During the registration/sign-up process, you provide us with personally identifiable information such as name, email address, etc. This information is used primarily to identify you in our service, which is necessary for the login process. The individual user account is based on e-mail addresses. We do not share this information with anyone, nor do we sell or market this information to any third party. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings and other promotional material; see the choice/opt-out section below. Projectplace reserves the right to use the registered information for CRM, sales and marketing activities unless the user has chosen to opt-out. 

Once you are logged in to the service you may enter personal information in your preferences, such as name, title, company or organization, postal address, phone and fax numbers, etc. This information is only shared with the people you choose to share it with within a project and is visible to us on your user account. We do not share this information with anyone, nor do we sell or market this information to any third party. 

In the purchase process, you provide us with personally identifiable information such as name, email address, postal address and phone number, etc. This information is used primarily for billing purposes, and to contact you in the case that a problem should occur with your account. This information is shared in discretion and under nondisclosure agreements with our billing partners, which is necessary since we have chosen to outsource invoicing, collection of receivables and credit card payments to partners. We do not market or sell this information to any third party and the partners of Projectplace will under no circumstances contact the users registered in our system for their own purposes. The information is collected and owned by Projectplace only. 

It is clearly indicated on our web sites if information is optional or mandatory. By registering optional information the user may benefit e.g. by receiving additional user guidelines and manuals via post, or faster support reply via telephone, mobile phone or fax. 

Our service contains links to other sites. Projectplace International AB is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Cookies**  
We use cookies to save your email address and language preference so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our service. Cookies are also used for the duration you are logged in to store session information. Please note that our service requires the use of cookies for the login procedure, so you cannot use the service if you set your browser to reject cookies. 

**Security**  
We recognize the importance our customers place on security. We exercise great care to see to that any information you enter or upload to your account is handled in a secure manner. Therefore, all communication between your computer and our servers is encrypted using SSL encryption technology. Furthermore, any document you upload to your account is securely transmitted (using SSL) and is then stored in an encrypted format. 

This service has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Internally, we restrict access to personally identifiable information to employees who need access to the information to do their job. All employees have to execute comprehensive nondisclosure agreements with us. Employees are not allowed to access your project data or uploaded documents. In fact, our extensive encryption procedures effectively prevents anyone (including our employees) to access this information. This information can only be accessed by the people you choose to share it with within a project. Backups of user and project data are scheduled on a regular basis and these backups are stored encrypted and safely locked up. For further information on the security of Projectplace.com we refer to our Security policy, which is available at <http://www.projectplace.com/terms/security_policy.html>[](http://www.projectplace.com/terms/security_policy.html)

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our service provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point of registration/sign-up for the service and also anytime when logged in by modifying user options. To modify your user options, go to your personal Preferences by clicking on the Preferences icon in the sidebar, and then the Options tab. 

Registered users who have not chosen to opt-out will receive periodical newsletters regarding our service. We may also use the information provided to contact the users for customer surveys or CRM, sales and marketing contacts. 

**Change/Modify**  
To change or modify any of the information provided in your user account, login to the service using your email address and your password. Go to your personal Preferences by clicking on the Personal icon in the sidebar. You can modify your profile by clicking on the Personal preferences icon and updating the fields under the different tabs displayed at the top. 

To change or modify any of the information provided in your project account (project owners/administrators only), login to the service using your email address and your password. Go to the project and click on the Administration icon. You can modify the project account information by updating the fields under the different tabs displayed at the top. 

**Deactivate**  
This service gives users the opportunity to remove their information from our database, to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service by logging into the service and removing the user account. 

**Changes in this policy**  
Projectplace reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. Users will be notified about changes in the Privacy Statement via our web sites and newsletters. 

**Additional information**  
Additional security information is available at <http://www.projectplace.com/terms/security_policy.html>.   
Additional information on the terms of use is available at <http://www.projectplace.com/terms/termsofuse.html>. 

**Contact information**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Projectplace International AB  
Drottninggatan 89  
113 60 Stockholm  
Sweden  
+46 8 586 302 00  

|  |
